A Guide to the Christopher C. Kraft Papers, 1941-1982
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- 1982
  - Commencement Address, VPI & SU, June 12 1982 (Box-folder 26-30)
  - Incoming Correspondence, January-June 1982 (Box-folder 26-31)
  - Outgoing Correspondence, January-June 1982 (Box-folder 26-32)
  - Personal Notes, July-August 1982 (Box-folder 26-33)
  - MS of Nystrom Article in VPI Alumni Magazine, July 1982 (Box-folder 26-34)
  - Rotary Club of Cincinnati, July 29, 1982 (Box-folder 26-35)
  - Award, Travel Hall of Fame (American Society of Travel Agents), October 11-12, 1982 (Box-folder 26-36)
  - Virginia Tech Correspondence, 1982 (Box-folder 26-41)
- The View from Mission Control Manuscript, c.1998
  - Chapters 1-3 (Box-folder 27-1)
  - Chapters 4-8 (Box-folder 27-2)
  - Chapters 9-13 (Box-folder 27-3)
  - Chapters 14-18 (Box-folder 27-4)
  - Chapters 19-23 (Box-folder 27-5)
  - Chapters 24-28 (Box-folder 27-6)
  - Chapters 29-33 (Box-folder 27-7)
  - Chapters 35-39 (Box-folder 27-8)
  - Chapters 35-39 (Box-folder 27-9)
  - Chapters 40-43 (Box-folder 27-10)
- Oversize Materials, 1941-1982
  - Drawings, blueprints and calculations/graphs (4 folders) (Folder 1 to 3, 6)
  - Charts, photographs, and event programs (Folder 4)
  - Newspapers and clippings (Folder 5)